**≥** serhiiraikovskyi33@outlook.com

☆ Jacksonville, United State

+1 774 320 1500

### About me

Prolific, Back end web developer with a passion for metrics and beating former "best-yets.", Well-versed in Back-End development. Recently throughout my 3 years career as a software developer I've focused on developing scalable and well documented code. I enjoy working collaboratively but can also run with projects on my own. Decreased rework by 18% and costs by 12% and consistently receive high user experience scores for all web development projects.

### **Skills**

HTML, CSS, Javascript, JQuery

Node, Express

PHP, Laravel, Yii2

Golang, Ruby on Rails

Python, Django

Git, GitHub, GitBucket

Linux (Ubuntu, CentOS)
Administration

AWS, MS Azure devOps, Vagrant

Docker, Kubernetes

### Education

Bachelor of Science (BS), Computer science

Saint Johns River State College, United State 2009 - 2013

# Serhii Raikovskyi

# Senior Web Developer

## Work experience

## Node.js developer

From November 2016 to September 2017 LEONI

- At this company, I was working on Node.js, React and Perl based services and applications.
- Some of my web apps included: Digital menuboards, business dashboards, online website plugins and APIs. I was also responsible for the managing my team's web infrastructure, SEO and website design.
- Most of the servers I dealt with were Debian/Ubuntu and I utilized DigitalOcean for off-site hosting.

### Backend developer

From October 2017 to April 2019 Luxoft

- At this job, I was responsible for developing, implementing and maintaining mostly internal web applications. I collaborated with technical and business staff in the development, testing, implementation and production support of enterprise applications.
- I was doing front-end development with HTML, CSS, Javascript and back-end development with Node.js. We utilized MongoDB and PostGresSQL. In addition to development, I also helped with end-user support for stakeholders and designated end users when escalated above our support teams.

### Full stack Developer

From April 2019 to October 2021 Baker Tilly US

- We primarily used MERN Stack. 20% of my work was doing front end development, 60% back end development and the remaining 20% was dev-ops/sys admin related tasks. We had a few system admins for a 50 persons + company.
- I was occasionally asked to do things such as migrating test database data between environments, doing jenkins builds/minor build plan tweaks, configuring webpack/or ui/unit testing frameworks.

#### Node.js Developer

From March 2021 to January 2023 Livingstone Research

- I was invited as a team leader at this company, participated in building this Website using Node.js, MongoDB, Alpine.js, API integration. Following common security practices and development design patterns
- Collaborated with 6 web developers, project manager, graphics designer, two QA engineers of the Livingstone company based on daily meeting & discussion, periodically updates via GitHub. Worked as senior development leader in a team
- Git Manage: Worked on sub-branch, Review code and merge to main branch.